fightersonlymagazine.co.uk 2010-11-10

# Fighters Only Magazine - The World's Greatest MMA Magazine - General Information - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy Our privacy policy relates only to information that we obtain about you. If you visit a Website operated by a third party through a hyperlink included in this Website, your information may be used differently by the operator of a linked Website.

### Cookies

A "cookie" is a message given to a Web browser by a Web server which is then stored by the browser in a text file on the hard drive of a user's computer. Each time the browser requests a page from the server, this message is sent back so that the user can be identified. Although we may use cookies during your visit to this Website, they do not contain any personally identifiable information about you.

### The information we will Collect

In addition to the information you provide on registration, we will collect:-

  * details about which of our services you utilise;
  * information each time you visit our Website;
  * information from the documents you complete.

Your information will be used to administer your requirements for information or services from us and to notify you about any changes to our Website. Occasionally, we may also use your details to inform you of other features, services and products we, or our group companies or our affiliate, can provide which we think you may be interested in and we may contact you by post, fax, email or telephone. If you do not wish to receive this additional information, you can let us know by ticking the appropriate box on the registration form.

### Keeping your data secure

We will keep your personal information confidential except to the extent that we are compelled to disclose it by law or to comply with an instruction of a regulatory body of competent jurisdiction. To comply with the requirements of the Data Protection Act 1998, we adhere to strict security procedures and have taken all appropriate measures to ensure that no unauthorised disclosures of your details are made to a third party without your permission and unauthorised access to it is prevented. In order to assist us with our security policy, you must adhere to the provisions set out in the security section of our terms and conditions.

### Use of an ISP

We reserve the right to appoint an Internet Service Provider ("ISP") to host this Website on our behalf which may be situated outside the European Economic Area (the "EEA"). In order to deliver the service to you, it may be necessary to transfer your information outside the EEA and by agreeing to our terms and conditions, you consent to any such transfer.
